Guide to the Records of the NYU TV and Media Services Video Recordings RG.38.16.1
New York University Archives
- Series II: Commencement and Founder's Day, 1995-2009
  - 167th NYU Commencement Master, 1999; 1 videocassettes (Box 16, Reel Project 71)
  - 167th NYU Commencement, 1999; 2 Betamax (Box 16, Reel Project 71)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day, 1999; 11 Sound_Disc-MiniDisc (Box 35)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1999; 9 videocassettes (Box 36)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes, 1999; 11 videocassettes (Box 37)
  - Stern Undergraduate Precommencement, 2000; 1 Betamax (Box 13, Reel Project 64)
  - 168th NYU Commencement, 2000; 10 videocassettes (Box 13, Reel Project 67)
  - 168th NYU Commencement, 2000; 1 VHS (Box 14, Reel Project 67)
  - 168th NYU Commencement, 2000; 2 Betamax (Box 14, Reel Project 67)
  - Stern Graduation, 2000; 1 VHS (Box 14, Reel Project 64)
  - Founders Day, 2000; 2 videocassettes (Box 15, Reel Project 63)
  - Gallatin Commencement Master, 2000; 2 videocassettes (Box 16, Reel Project 72)
  - School of Continuing & Professional Studies Commencement, 2000; 2 videocassettes (Box 16, Reel Project 75)
  - 169th NYU Commencement, 2001; 3 VHS (Box 14, Reel Project 70)
  - Founder's Day, 2001; 3 videocassettes (Box 15, Reel Project 63)
  - 169th Commencement Exercises NYU 2001, 10 May 2001; 2 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - 169th NYU Commencement Master, 2001; 4 videocassettes (Box 16, Reel Project 70)
  - 169th NYU Commencement Master, 2001; 11 videocassettes (Box 17, Reel Project 70)
    Barcode: 31142042272909
  - 169th NYU Commencement, 2001; 10 videocassettes (Box 18, Reel Project 70)
    Barcode: 31142042272917
  - Gallatin Commencement Master, 2001; 2 videocassettes (Box 19, Reel Project 72)
  - "School of Continuing & Professional Studies Class Day Exercises Master, 2001; 1 videocassettes (Box 19, Reel Project 69)
  - Founder's Day, 2002; 3 VHS (Box 13, Reel Project 63)
  - 170th NYU Commencement, 2002; 2 VHS (Box 13, Reel Project 68)
  - Founder's Day, 2002; 4 VHS (Box 14, Reel Project 63)
  - Founder's Day Master, 2002; 3 videocassettes (Box 15, Reel Project 63)
  - School of Continuing & Professional Studies Commencement Master, 2002; 4 videocassettes (Box 19, Reel Project 69)
  - 170th NYU Commencement, 2002; 8 videocassettes (Box 19, Reel Project 68)
  - 170th NYU Commencement, 2002; 18 videocassettes (Box 20, Reel Project 68)
    Barcode: 31142042272933
  - 171st NYU Commencement, 2003; 12 videocassettes (Box 21, Reel Project 76)
  - 171st NYU Commencement, 2003; 3 VHS (Box 71, Reel Project 76)
  - 171st NYU Commencement Master, 2003; 8 videocassettes (Box 22, Reel Project 76)
    Barcode: 31142042272958
  - 172nd NYU Commencement Master, 2004; 7 videocassettes (Box 23, Reel Project 78)
  - Gallatin Graduation 2004, 10 May 2004; 1 DVCAM (Box 71)
  - College of Arts & Sciences (CAS) Commencement Master, May 11, 2004; 3 videocassettes (Box 23, Reel Project 80)
  - 172nd NYU Commencement Master, 2004; 17 videocassettes (Box 24, Reel Project 78)
    Barcode: 31142042272974
  - 173rd NYU Commencement Master, 2005; 16 videocassettes (Box 25, Reel Project 81)
    Barcode: 31142042272982
  - 173rd NYU Commencement Master, 2005; 6 videocassettes (Box 26, Reel Project 81)
    Barcode: 31142042272990
  - NYU College of Arts and Science Bacculaureatre, 5 Dec 2005; 1 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - CAS Baccalaureate Ceremony, 4 Dec 2006; 2 DVCAM (Box 75)
  - 2006 Steinhardt Commencement Master, 22 Jun 2006; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2006, 22 videocassettes (Box 38, Box 103)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2007, 14 videocassettes (Box 39, Box 102)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2007, 10 videocassettes (Box 40)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2007, 11 videocassettes (Box 41)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2007, 8 videocassettes (Box 42)
  - The Churchill School Graduation, 22 Jun 2007; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008, 12 videocassettes (Box 43)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008, 17 videocassettes (Box 44)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008, 15 videocassettes (Box 45)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008, 0 videocassettes (Box 46)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008, 12 videocassettes (Box 63)
  - Commencement 2008 (Box 83)
  - CAS Winter Baccalaureate, 8 Dec 2008; 1 DVCAM (Box 78)
  - 2008 Steinhardt Doctoral Commencement, 12 May 2008; 4 DVCAM (Box 69)
  - Commencement 2009, 24 videocassettes (Box 82, Box 86)
  - Commencement 2009 (Box 85)
  - Commencement 2009 (Box 84)
  - NYU Logo: Torch 1831, undated; 1 Betacam_SP (Box 13, Reel Project 61)
    Barcode:31142042272867
  - NYU Logo: Bobcat, undated; 1 DVCAM (Box 13, Reel Project 61)
  - Silver Convocation, undated; 2 VHS (Box 13, Reel Project 62)
  - School of Continuing & Professional Studies Ceremonies, undated; 3 videocassettes (Box 14, Reel Project 69)
  - NYU Logo: Torch Master, undated; 1 videocassettes (Box 19, Reel Project 61)
  - NYU Logo: Tiffany, undated; 1 videocassettes (Box 21, Reel Project 61)
  - Unlabelled Commencement, undated; 2 VHS (Box 26, Reel Project 82)
  - CAS Winter Baccalaureate, 2010 Dec 6; 1 DVCAM (Box 90)
  - 1996 Commencement Video Rough Cut (Box 94)
  - NYU Commencement 1996: ISO CAM 3 Tape 2 (Box 94)